https://www.board.com/en/privacy-policy

Search in board.comHomePrivacy policyPrivacy policyThe General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), which came into force on 25 May 2018, aims to guarantee that the personal data of physical persons is processed in compliance with the rights, fundamental freedoms and dignity of persons, with particular reference to confidentiality and personal identity. Board International SA and its subsidiaries (“Board”), pay particular attention to the way in which personal information is used and shared and it is therefore important to inform you of the adopted privacy policy.Processing of personal data means the collection, recording, organisation, conservation, processing, alteration, selection, retrieval, comparison, use, disclosure, erasure, distribution, interconnection and any other processing which is useful for the performance of the specific service requested (the “Service”).1. Personal information we collect from users 1.1 Board collects the personal information provided by users when sending the contact forms on the website www.board.com (the “Website”) (for example, relating to the "Careers", "Free Demo", “Training and Support” or "Events" sections) and in particular:name and job title or contact information including the e-mail address and telephone number;personal information such as address, postcode, country, position;other information relating to surveys or offers sent to customers.This information falls under the definition of personal data, i.e. any information concerning an identified or identifiable physical person (the “Data subject”); identifiable refers to physical persons who can be identified, directly or indirectly, with particular reference to data such as the name, identification number, data concerning their location, an online ID or one or more characteristic elements of his or her physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity (the “Personal data”).1.2 The Website uses cookies, as described in more detail in the Cookies Policy.2. Purposes of the processing2.1 The Personal Data provided by you at the time of registering with the Service, or otherwise acquired during the activities performed by us, may be processed, for purposes linked to the provisions of the Service and in particular to respond to requests sent by you to Board (for example, to send information materials, to be contacts or for a demo or sales offer, etc.). After registration, Board may send you e-mails relating to similar services to those provided subsequently to your request for the Service. You may object to the sending of e-mails at any time.2.2 Your Personal data will be used to periodically send promotional e-mails (using the e-mail address provided by you), if you accept this Privacy Policy when submitting the form. These e-mails may concern new products, events, special offers or other information Board thinks may interest you. The above communications may be sent to you also by third parties in the Board company group to whom Board may provide the Personal Data provided by you.2.3 Your Personal Data may also be used for profiling, through the use of cookies and following acceptance in this sense by you. The acceptance of the use of cookies is given at the start when clicking on “Accept cookies” and closing the banner, as better explained in the Cookies Policy.3. Methods of processing3.1 Your Personal Data are collected by the parties indicated in point 6. and the related processing is done using manual or computerised automated instruments with logics strictly linked to the purposes described above and in any case to guarantee the security and confidentiality of the data.4. Optional nature of the provision of data4.1 The provision of Personal Data by you is absolutely optional and does not represent a legal requirement; however, in some cases, the provision of your Personal Data could be required in order to provide the Service you have requested.4.2 As regards the effects of the non-acceptance or disabling of the cookies, please refer to the terms of the Cookies Policy.5. Categories of persons to whom the personal data may be disclosed5.1 The Personal Data collected for the purpose of the provision of the Service (point 2.1) may be disclosed to companies performing functions that are strictly linked and instrumental to the functioning of the Service, and in particular to respond to your requests. Such data may be transferred to associated companies and/or companies in the Board group or third parties even located outside the European Community, where there is a decision of suitability (guarantee of an appropriate level of protection) by the European Commission.5.2 The Personal Data collected for the purposes listed in point 2 may be transferred to third parties in the Board Group or other third parties (located inside or outside the European Community), also for sale or attempted sale, i.e. all purposes of a lawful commercial and/or statistical nature. The list of persons to whom your personal data have been disclosed may be requested from Board using the e-mail address given in point 7.4.6. Controller, Processors and RepresentativesData Controller or Controller refers to the physical or legal person, public authority, service or other body which, individually or with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of processing are determined by law by the European Union and the Member States, the Controller or the specific criteria applicable to his or her appointment may be established by the law of the European Union and the Member States;6.1. The Controllers are Board International SA with registered office in Piazza Bernasconi 5, Chiasso, Ticino 6830, Switzerland and the other companies in the Board group which work autonomously and independently in the processing of personal data.6.2 The Controllers appoint external Processors to achieve the purposes specified in point 2. It is possible to request a complete list of external Processors by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address specified in point 7.4 of this policy.6.3 The Controllers have appointed their own employees and collaborators to process the data.6.4 Data subjects may exercise their rights towards each Controller.7. Rights of the data subjects7.1 You have the right, at any time, to obtain confirmation from the Controller as to whether or not personal data concerning you is being processed, to know its origin, purposes and methods of processing; you also have the right to request the updating, correction, integration, erasure, transformation into an anonymous form, the suspension of any data processed in violation of the relevant legislation, including those which are no longer necessary to pursue the purposes for which they were collected and/or subsequently processed.7.2 You have the right to object, wholly or partially, to the processing of your personal data for legitimate reasons, even where this is still relevant for the purpose for which they were collected, and to the processing of your personal data for the purpose of commercial information or the sending or advertising materials or direct sales or for the execution of market research or commercial communication.7.3 You have the right to receive the Personal Data concerning you provided knowingly and actively through the use of the Service, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance.7.4 To exercise your rights please write to the specific e-mail address: privacy@board.com.7.5 Please not that you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority.7.6 If you no longer wish to receive notifications via e-mail from Board and wish to unsubscribe from the newsletter, you may do so by clicking on the "erasure" link at the bottom of each e-mail sent by Board.8. Period for which the personal data is stored8.1 Your personal data will be conserved in hard copy and/or electronic/computerised/optical format for the time strictly necessary to meet the purposes listed in point 2, in compliance with the laws in force. Board has defined the specific duration of the conservation of data for each type of data collected. At the end of such periods, Board will definitively erase your data.8.2 If you request the erasure of your Personal Data from the Website. Please not that such data will be conserved for the purpose of the investigation and prosecution of breaches for a period of no more than 12 months from the date of communication, and will subsequently be erased safely in an anonymised and irreversible manner. Please also note that for the same purposes the data relating to telematic traffic, excluding in any case the contents of the communications, shall be kept for a period of no more than 12 months following the date of communication.9. Amendments9.1 This Privacy Policy may be subject to amendments. If substantial amendments are made to the use of your Personal Data, Board will notify you by publishing a notice on the Website and/or by sending you an e-mail.10. ContactsFor any informing or request relating to this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the e-mail address privacy@board.com, or write to us by post at the following address: Board International, Piazza Bernasconi 5, Chiasso, Ticino 6830, Switzerland.Want to see Board in action?Request a demoWant to see Board in action? Request a free demo!×
